This is Ganesan, Shekar's partner.  He
has two or three guava groves of his own.
Hey Chinnaswamy, is this there?
Oh, my God,
how long has it been since dawn?
Look at the children in the village, what they do to
go to school and hunt for jobs
.  Hey,
I'm sorry, I drank this coffee water
.  That man is.
This mother's lamentation is enough.  There is
no need to talk about Pandya separately.  I'm going to continue
drinking and smoking pot
.  [Music]
Hold on tight, Pandi.
Hey, look there, don't be shy,
this is a famous person.  [Music]
I'm working on a wire machine in Temperariya.  He feels like
God is the one who gives light to this town
.
How?
[Music]
This is called Ayyappan.
50 paise stone.
Isn't this a big deal?
This is the only wholesale store in this town.
Give me 50 cents.
This shop
was founded with money from their father's retirement from the military.
Hello, hello, Galle
.
This is Kalimuthu.  The financier of this town.
Oh, I should have
come to this shop sooner.
He arrived late one day.  Even though he
arrived late, he arrived early and got off.
The car is expensive.
Before Ivan finishes his sentence, he has to
say one thing.  These seven people are from the
same town, but have different amenities and different castes.
One thing that unites them all is
kabaddi.  Kabaddi is a game played on this soil
.  If only there were land and people to play this game
.  Our
accountant is here.
They know how to play.
One in 100 people doesn't know how to win.
Until today, I have never won a single soap bar while traveling abroad
.  Unfortunately,
they too are dreaming of winning one day for me.   That's just how
life is, that's why the
game keeps going.
They have two points in their team with one bonus point and another point.   The
Kabaddi team player
has given up a point within the bounds of the earth.  The son of the earth is
singing.
He has raised the intimacy of two people to five.   The
team leader
has brought the opponents.
Four wins,
Kabaddi, Kabaddi, Kabaddi, he's back without a win. The
player has earned another victory point.
[Laughter] The
vanilla player is singing at lightning speed. He has
earned the first victory point for his team. One point, that's it. He's making
himself drunk, making tea so that no one will come to the little bar.
Hey, little boy, what's up,
what's this?
I said, "Oh, it's a good day, no one will come to the store."
All the people who ask the woman at home are my
head.  Okay,
have some tea, mate.  Aren't we the only ones who can do that
?  I don't want anything, just leave.
Where is Thirulakada?   Is
it true?   I'll be back in
a minute to ask for my bride
.  Okay, okay, come quickly.
My golden princess, Pasangallam, is
calling out to me.  I'm going to the grocery store and I'm coming back
.   Even when it's
good, I'll
tell you to watch the market, if you don't want to be bothered.
Saturday is over.  Come here,
sit here and take your life.
I'll come back as soon as I get home, Lakshmi, wo
n't you come?   Wait, I'll
come.
Okay, Lakshmi, go quickly and buy
it. Okay, okay, okay. It seems that Subramani will have
emptied everything in the Ponga satti by the time he gets here. It's not like Mappala is going to come. It's
time to
buy it. When did you come? We just
came. Are
you okay? Are you okay? Get
in and eat. No, no. Oh, stay still. Hey, don't
talk. I'm going to collect you. Let's go to the
house. Let's go and take a bath. Come on, my
husband's fingers have started. Come on,
okay,
buy it.
[Laughter]
Now you know what it is.
Then, if you blow the whistle, you'll be fine. If you're out, come out. Come out. Oh, don't
come so fast in a slow race. Don't
fall down so fast in fear of the danger. Our
pot.  Breaking competition [Encouragement]
[Applause] If you
knock, you will be a hundred times better
[Applause][Encouragement]
Clap your hands Come on, come  If you don't tell me to
speak locally, I'll tell you that it won't happen. Let it go. Let it go. Let it go. Let it go.
Next, an elephant took a step to break the pot. He
thought it was the wrong path. He thought it was the right path. He said, "Hey, sir, it's going.
It's not going. It's the boy who's running. The hammer is in
our hand. It's breaking. Hey, my friend, my friend, don't tie it.
Why don't you just tie it up? You're the only one who's going to
ruin it.
Hey, my friend, I won't break my promise to my dead father.
Then
my mother-in-law came to Thiruval and sat in my house and
took my usury. She was the
only one who
said, "Saba, the groom is right. I
won't even give you a tea loan. Don't you know, don't you know, don't you know, don't you know, don't you know, I won't
come. I know very
well. I don't know
how to tie anything. I know
a little.
You will tie your eyes in your afterlife. You will not tie your eyes. You will not tie your eyes. You will tie your eyes without tying your eyes. Even though you are a child who is
wearing a phone, it
seems that the little girl who is now coming towards the table for the sake of the husband has broken the tie.
Next in line is Chithappa Pulipandi, who has broken pots many times in Kanyakapatti and is also a
Silambatta player. It is a sight to behold to see
that tiger breaking pots now
[laughter].
Oh my, is he like Keezh Usurukka?
Next in line is
Marimuthu, who is constantly losing in the competition while everyone else is
getting ready.
[Encouragement]
Please raise your hands to Marimuth and break this curse.
I've been talking to you too.  [Applause]
[Cheer] Come on, step aside and finish pushing like this
.  It seems like he's not coming.  It
looks like a body.  Mariamuthu, who was about to break the pot,
woke them up and said, "What is
this house? Go there, Padiya.
Think carefully and
break it like a poppa. [Applause] Medhu [Applause]
is getting ready to break the pot.  Now the pan is
lifted.  Everyone woke up and said, "
Satti, Satti, it's on the bottom floor, Marisu is on the top floor, he's
sitting on the top floor
."  Now the pot is
going to be lifted.  [Applause]
What's up?   Is
it a bug or is it a bug that will disappear?
Let's see.
Your car is finished.
[Encouragement]
Here comes Subramani, don't you see
now, Pandi.  "Wada Subramani,
then you left the old lady alone at home and
came back. "
Yes,
that's what you asked."
No, I just wanted to know.
You're not coming to play either.  I have a little work to do in the morning
.  You too, do not come and fear, for the image of Lord
Ganesha, who is causing fear, has gone to call.
Papa,
don't leave this one match, I'll leave the soap and go play kabaddi.
Come and eat kabaddi, kabaddi. Papa, this one
match, Papa, if you
were just tied up, why are you beating me with your hands and feet?
I've seen how you play kabaddi for me.
Papa, the door is far away. This one match,
Papa,
this one person is so annoying, what do you
think? Will you come now or
not?
My two little girls are coming, they're calling me
.
Hey, everyone, come and play.   Oh my god, you've just
arrived.   You're here
.  Hey, my god, he's the
only one who's coming alone.
Hey Ganesh, where is
he? Your father has
locked him in the house.
What do you say?
He won't come, won't the groom come?
Hey, what are you doing now?
I won't come, my friend. I'll buy this match
.
Hey, little one,
I'm
a man of ten, wouldn't it be enough if you just came and stood there?
Hey, what are you playing?  What did my grandmother do to me?
Hey, what is this guy
talking, making up and dressing up? Did
he come to a beautiful woman who was amazed and stood there? Did he stand there, amazed and stood there? Did he tie a sari and make up and dress up? Can you count it
correctly? Here are 35 and
here are 37. It's
not enough.
Then take ₹100. Take
what are you waiting for? Take 100 rupees.
What is 100 rupees? Take 100 rupees. We gave 100 rupees. There is no
discount at all. No, don't scold the prota.
Oh, let's go. It's
like you're here. This is a line
bet. A
man said he wanted to eat 50 prota and made a
bet and went away. Shall
we come to the bet?
Anyone can come except this generous person.
What kind of bandana does
a person have to eat 50 protons?  If
any of you eat it, I will
give you ₹100.  You
don't have to pay for Prota.
You've gone mad.  You have to
give me ₹100.  I have to
tie a child to a prota that I ate and ate,
what's
50 prota?
Yes,
I'm ready for famine.   He miscalculated by
looking at his figure
.
Madna Supplier
[Music]
Two districts are enough to
oppose them. Where is Dindigul district?
Prota, will they stay until you come?
Go and take Prota and say, "Oh, this is it,
Salna, cook it?"
[Music] Okay, stab it.
[Music] Eat,
eat
Go and get it.  Dingu [music] Dingu dinguta
dinguta
hey da da
[music]
Enough.  I ate 50.
Hey, I've eaten 42 Tandas.
I ate 50, my dear.
Hey, don't count the number of forts, it's 42.
Don't you know I ate 50?   I do
n't know if I
ate 42.   It's impossible
.  You are welcome
.  I will not agree.  I
ate.  Destroy all the castles,
I will eat from the beginning.  You
go and get it.  Hey,
you go and put on a coat.
Let's add Anna to that.   The
Vanilla Kabaddi team from Dindigul district is
thriving on the pitch
.
Brother, we have an audience, 11
people are clapping their hands.
Kabaddi Kabaddi [Laughter]
Kanyakumari Police first point, a
great start to
Kabaddi, which opponent? Kabaddi   Can we
sit down for a while again?
[Cheers]
[Laughter]
Two more winning catches for the
rider line.  If the ball goes beyond the
boundary line, it is out.   The
police team is leading with nine points.
Hello sir, who is the point sir? They have
dropped everything. They have taken it by making a comedy.
Where did I get off?
He was the one who said that they will play very well.
[Encouragement] Stay up, stay up, play
Kabaddi Kabaddi Kabaddi Kabaddi Kabaddi Kabaddi
Kabaddi
Police Give it to everyone who got three points,
give it to everyone  My little
sister Perusa, I'm
not going to finish it today, but
that little girl's mother-in-law has just given
her daughter a hug.  The
chairman's method of thinking of the boy who tied it was that the girl, Thenmoshi, also
works as a teacher at the Palani School.
Honey is not a language,
honey is
very important.
Even the chairman's sister
must have spoken to the boy.
This is a bit of a distant relative.
Okay, sir, we'll leave right away.
What's wrong,
call me Uncle Sara, with all due respect, my friend.
Uncle Sethanda Shekara.
How is that?
Call me "Hey, uncle" and get off the phone.
Brother, what are you saying? Uncle,
please hide your face and give me a cup of
coffee.
Brother, you are the one who drank that seventh
number. It's very good, brother.
Okay, uncle, we're
leaving.
Okay, we're all one in the same
.  We
can cook dinner for everyone tomorrow.  Definitely come.   Okay, okay,
brother, everyone will come.
Okay.   I'll
come and pick you up tomorrow.  Hey, don't
come back,
what are you all doing here?
Our own children have come to play and
win, aren't
they, are they, our own children? How are they, my dear
Look,
you're all from the same village,
Grandma.
Which goddamn ruler are you?
That's where you come from, are
you from the lower street?
They were all guests who came to our house
.
What do you care about which street they are on, which temple they worship?
Oh, why do
n't you ask what caste you are?
What are you doing, asking about caste?   You
can only move fast if you learn to lift both caste and religion and not burden them.   Come
inside,
I'll walk quickly and tear you apart.
Go
join the party and say that there is no caste, no religion, no
age. No matter
how much you say, your intellect doesn't want to be
spoiled like your house.
Listen and eat.
[Music]
What, brother? Is it spicy?
That's not all.  What's the idea? I remembered
my father. I've
never eaten any of your good food. Time flies. I
want to make porridge like this.
What's the point? I'll come and make it.
It's just a mouthful. Brother, you
eat it. May
everything go well for you and your mother.
What are you studying in college?
Which college is
Meenakshi College?